I will extract the evidence from him.
There's a way to do it...
Watch out!
We found two types of glucose inhibitors
in his blood.
Someone must have drugged him.
And you suspect me?
You think she's your friend?
Don't forgot how Ben died.
Don't you feel guilty when you see her?
If someone inadvertently
spilled the beans about something,
what would happen?
Ask yourself how I treated you.
You're very good to me...
You gave me food and shelter
and took good care of me.
I went to jail and my money was confiscated.
I only want what is rightfully mine.
Won't you help me?
Of course...
Good girl!
Ben had two women in his life.
If the mistress doesn't have the money,
the wife must have it.
Go talk to the wife in the hospital.
I will.
Mary, let me help you.
Hi, I'm Cathy's friend.
Suet?
Out! Get the hell out!
Get out! You...
What are you doing here?
I was going to help her pick that up...
Get out!
Just go!
Is that necessary?
Just go.
How can you be friends with her?
She's with those thugs who killed Ben.
She's a baddie.
She called me Mary.
You told her about me?
No. I'm friends with her because of Ben.
Precisely because of Ben,
you should stay away from her.
Calm down. Don't get so agitated.
What are you doing here?
I meant to have lunch with you
and you didn't call me back.
That's why I came over.
Mary doesn't want you to contact me.
She has no right to choose your friends.
You shouldn't come here.
I'm really busy today.
You should leave.
Are you better?
Better find out where the money is.
Cathy, you're back!
Are you tired?
I made soup. I'll heat it up for you.
Sorry, I didn't expect Mary to react
like that when she saw me.
I didn't mean it.
You know I don't use my head.
Please don't be mad.
I have good news.
My tutor at the hairstyling school
wants to recommend me to study
styling in Seoul.
Let's go together.
I can't get away.
You don't have money?
Thanks.
Thank you.
Did you leave me the keycard?
Yes, it's for you.
Is this about the legal loopholes?
Don't ask. Just keep it for me.
But we're still tracking down the $1.8M
Lau Yue-bun received for money laundering.
The money should be handed in to the Police.
But you risked your life for it.
I know what to do.
I will spend it on Mary.
I can't leave even if I have the money.
Why not, if money is not the issue?
I can't just drop everything.
Because of Mary?
Is it worth it?
You intend to spend the rest of
your life like this?
Give up your life and your dream?
My dream is to be a nurse.
I know you're a good person.
But don't you think this is too much?
Do you really want to do this?
Or only because of Ben?
It's one thing if he gave you money.
If he didn't, how can you take on
the burden of a patient forever?
You're still young, you don't understand.
I'm tired. I'll go shower.
What happened all of a sudden?
Did you call Dr. Chung?
Yes, he's on his way.
It's a relapse of her GBS,
Guillain- Barre Syndrome.
She was making good progress this week.
Why did this happen so suddenly?
That's the nature of GBS.
Her condition is now stabilized
and she's out of danger.
But the relapse affected her
respiratory muscles.
She'll have trouble breathing
and heart arrhythmia.
Should we give her IVIG like last time?
IVIG is the most effective treatment.
But it's expensive.
Do it. Money is not an issue.
She authorized me to make decisions for her,
to use whatever means to treat her.
OK, I'll set it up.
Thanks.
Ben risked his life for the money.
For him, you must hang in there.
You're late? More OT?
I'll reheat the food for you.
No need. I'll just grab something,
take a shower and go back to the hospital.
Why are you so busy?
Her condition took a turn for the worse.
I want to be with her.
The next few days are crucial.
If Mary is in trouble, she'll get the money.
If I follow her, I'll find the money.
This is where she keeps Ben's money!
Where the hell are you? Get over here.
I told you to look for the money.
Did you find it?
I have not seen her with any money.
Maybe she spent it already.
Use your head. She spent $1.8M?!
That broad must have it.
But I looked everywhere. There is nothing.
You don't want to help me, right?
Of course not!
If you don't want to help me,
I have other ways to make her cough it up.
I have another plan to make her talk.
Let me try.
He doesn't seem to believe me.
Can't let him know where Cathy lives.
Even if your friend wants someone
to share the flat,
you don't need to leave in such a hurry.
If I don't hurry,
what if she found someone else?
I'd miss a good deal.
Male or female?
Girlfriend.
Let's catch a taxi over there.
Cathy, are you OK?
Did you send someone to run us over?
Yes.
I told you I have another plan.
What plan? Let's hear it.
I was thinking...
Stop jerking me around.
You won't tell me where the broad lives
because you don't want me to find her.
You think I don't know?
You claimed to have a plan,
then you ghosted me.
You want the money for yourself
and then skip town, right?
No! I really looked everywhere
but didn't find the money.
Are you trying to help the broad?
You took me in and gave me money.
I know you're the good guy.
Cathy is in worse shape than I am.
The dude is dead,
and she's stuck with the invalid wife.
You think I'm a moron like Dummy and Shek?
You had their heads spinning
just by talking to them.
Listen, I let you hang around,
only because I need you to help
them let off steam,
so those morons would do my bidding.
Now that you're useless to me,
I'm going to make you a whore.
Come here...
Listen, if I could kill Ben,
I can certainly kill you.
If you won't tell me where the money is,
you're not leaving, do you hear me?
Why are you calling me so late?
Cathy, help me!
Go! Drive!
OK!
What happened? How did you get roughed up?
I'm sorry, Cathy.
There's something I haven't told you...
I'm in contact with Brother Kin.
You said you wanted to live a normal life.
Why do you want to stick with him?
I thought he was good to me.
That's why I listen to him.
But he was using me the whole time.
He rammed my head against the wall
just like he did when he killed Ben.
What? He killed Ben?
What exactly happened?
You must tell me the whole story.
Ben came to see Brother Kin.
As usual, I was sleeping
with my headphones on.
Then the battery of my phone died,
and I heard a racket downstairs.
I went down to check it out.
Stop staring. Give me a hand.
What?
Lift his legs.
Go back up.
Lie down.
Put the headphones back on.
Remember, we were asleep the whole time.
We never went downstairs
and didn't know what happened, OK?
My mind went blank.
Brother Kin told me to pretend
I didn't know anything.
I really didn't want to know.
There's a lot of blood. He's...dead!
Brother Kin...get up!
Brother Kin, we're screwed...
Get up...don't sleep anymore.
Get up!
Brother Kin...
What's wrong?
We killed Ben.
Stay here. I'll go look.
Hurry...
Come on...
I didn't go down and thought I'd be OK.
Brother Kin, the air con is on high.
We sprayed loads of air freshener.
People won't smell the body so quickly.
Brother Kin, I had nothing to do with this.
Do I have to go on the run?
You watched while it happened
and you moved Ben's body.
What do you think?
It's too late to back out now.
Just go!
There's a citywide manhunt for us.
We can't stay in hiding much longer.
Those two morons thought they did it anyway.
Just pin it on them.
What do you have in mind?
I want you to sneak out, go to the Police
and rat on them.
What? Are you sure?
I'm wanted by the Police too.
Would they believe me?
Don't worry,
we can all prove we were sleeping upstairs
and didn't know what happened.
They're bound to ask you who
solicited to commit murder.
Tell them I did,
but you heard me telling them the next day
that I was only kidding. Remember that!
I knew it wasn't that simple.
Tai Yat-kin was not only the instigator,
he was also the killer.
I need to call the Police.
No, you can't.
I perjured myself,
the cops would arrest me too.
Then why did you cover up for him?
I didn't know any better then.
I thought he was the good guy and
wouldn't hurt me.
But it was only after I met you,
I realized what a good person is like.
After Brother Kin got out of jail,
I didn't want him to contact me.
But he insisted you kept Ben's money.
He wouldn't leave me alone
and forced me to find out from you
where the money was.
I knew you kept the money
in the mini storage.
But I didn't tell him.
Because I know you need the money
for Mary's treatment.
At least you came to your senses
and didn't tell him everything.
I didn't want him to follow me
because I didn't want him to know
where you live.
That's why I moved out.
But he still found me...
You're saying he sent someone
to run us over?
Yes! Don't go to the Police!
He's crazy.
Besides, Ben's money is illegal.
You can't tell the Police.
I will extract the evidence from him.
How? I can't go back to him.
There's a way to do it...
But it'll be too risky for you.
No, I shouldn't have ideas like that.
It's too risky. I can't let you do it.
You want to nail him?
OK, if you want to nail him,
let's nail this creep. I'll help you.
Just tell me what to do.
I told you to watch her. What happened?
I remember I forgot to buy smokes for you.
You need two people to do that?
Brother Kin, I finally found out.
About time you showed up.
Don't get upset.
I have something to tell you.
I ran away because I suddenly remember
a few days ago, Cathy was sneaking around
doing something under the stove
in the kitchen.
I was wondering if that's where
she kept the money.
I know she worked the late shift last night,
so I hurried home and I found the money.
I brought it to you right away.
I had to lean on you to get anything done.
I saw cops around when I was coming here.
I was afraid they'd stop me but they didn't.
Where's the rest?
That's all I found. Keep it in a safe place.
I'm hungry.
Go get something to eat.
Look at all the beer. Let's have a drink
to celebrate finding the money.
Come on...
Don't be vicious like last time,
you had me scared.
You threatened to make me a whore.
Were you joking?
You saw me when I'm pissed off.
Don't get on my bad side.
When you said "If I could kill Ben,
I can certainly kill you",
were you kidding?
Brother Kin is good for his words.
You're such a bragger.
I bet Ben went crazy last time
and it was self-defense.
That weasel Ben deserved to die.
Hey, Ben...
Open the safe and get me the money.
No, what can you do about it?
I saw the nail on the wall
and I rammed his head right into it.
Those two morons thought they killed him
and took the rap.
Let's not talk about that.
Have another one.
Bloody hell, you made a recording?
You think you'll get me talking?
(Suet)
Hello, Suet?
That bloody recording pen won't
send me to jail.
Help me...Let me out...
You want her back? Bring the money.
Don't call the Police or she's dead.
Help...
OK...I'll give it to you.
Do not hurt her, you hear me?
Watch it. It's dangerous to drink and drive.
Shut up.
I'm dead if I don't have the money.
Well?
You want to play games? Where's the rest?
I used some of it.
This is all I have left.
You can take the money,
but I get the girl.
You'll get her when you give me the rest.
Hey...
Get in...
Hey!
Watch out!
Suet...
Wake up...
The victim Tai Yat-kin is certified.
That weasel Ben deserved to die.
I saw the nail on the wall
and I rammed his head right into it.
Those two morons thought they killed him
and took the rap.
Luckily, you had two recording pens
and managed to record
Tai Yat-kin's confession.
It was Suet's idea.
I didn't know beforehand.
We still don't recommend taking such risks.
You're lucky you got away,
next time, you could be dead.
I know.
Maybe this is his retribution.
At first, I was worried
even if we had incriminating evidence,
we may not be able to convict him.
Gogo Sir, you said one cannot be charged
with the same offense twice.
Maybe a killer should pay with his life.
At least justice is served for Ben.
The long arm of the law will get you.
One more thing...though the money
went up in smoke with the car,
but according to procedures,
you must declare the amount.
It's around $300K, that's my entire savings.
What a shame it went up in smoke!
No, at least nobody is hurt.
You were just getting better.
I'm sorry I had to transfer you.
Don't be. You can look after me.
It's the least I could do.
Gogo Sir was right.
You could have died, all because of me.
Still, I volunteered to do it.
As long as you got your wish.
Thank you.
You won't need to live in fear anymore.
Cathy, I made so many mistakes in the past,
I hope you can forgive me
and accept me as your friend.
Don't be silly. We're friends already.
Let's move on, OK?
Yes!
Dr. Chung said your treatment
is very effective.
He's confident you'll make more progress.
You may recover.
Really?
Thanks so much for taking such risks
and kept Ben's money to save me.
And you avenged him.
I think we have Suet to thank.
I didn't expect her to take such risks.
I guess I was wrong about her.
I was biased against her at first.
She's actually just a kid longing for
someone to care about her
and be nice to her.
Cathy, what are you doing?
The bag was dirty,
I was going to empty it out and wash it.
No, I can manage.
Speaking like a true professional,
who doesn't want anyone to touch your tools.
You usually sleep like a log,
and very hard to wake you up.
How come you woke up so easily just now?
I don't know. Maybe I slept too much
in the hospital.
Besides, so much happened lately,
I still feel jittery.
I have the day off today.
Let's go out and relax?
Great!
Where do you want to go?
Looks like you want to go to the beach.
Yes, I know it's childish, but fun.
I also want to take loads of pictures.
OK!
Hello?
OK, I'll come in. Bye!
What is it?
Sorry, a colleague is sick
and they need me to fill in a shift.
It's OK. Go to work.
We'll do this next time.
Crash...I found it.
You're alone? Where's your family?
My wife is at home.
My kids are working.
You have kids?
Who came with you?
Chi...there you are!
I was looking for you. Let's go.
You're his wife?
No, I work for his family.
You shouldn't be running around.
Your wife is waiting at the door. Come on...
Does he really have kids?
Yes, Chi is a happy man!
Let's go...say goodbye!
Come on...
Miss Tse, we have questions for you.
What are glucose inhibitors for?
They help diabetics control their
blood sugar level.
What happens if you take an overdose?
You'll have low blood sugar level,
general fatigue, dizziness, blurry vision.
In serious cases, you'll go into
hypoglycemic shock.
Why do you ask?
We suspect Tai Yat-kin's death
was not an accident.
Forensics examined the car.
There was no sign of mechanical failure.
But his autopsy report showed
a high dosage of glucose inhibitor
in his blood.
We suspect the low blood sugar level
made him unconscious
and he lost control of the car.
Hold on...Suet told me
Tai Yat-kin drank heavily the night before.
Alcohol can increase the drug effect
which may cause hypoglycemic shock.
Or after the intake of alcohol,
he overdosed on the drugs.
Situations like that happened before
to other patients.
Neither is possible.
We found two types of
glucose inhibitors in his blood.
There was no record of him
switching his meds.
We also found a bottle of
oolong tea in the car
that contained one of the
glucose inhibitors.
We're quite certain he was drugged.
This person knows Tai Yat-kin well
and that he was diabetic.
This person was smart enough
to use a glucose inhibitor
to cause an accident
to cover up the murder.
How can ordinary people get the drugs?
Maybe someone who works in a hospital?
And you suspect me?
Suet, if you don't start rinsing,
you won't finish in time
and the tutor will dock your score.
Blood! Blood!
And you suspect me?
Tai Yat-kin killed the love of your life.
You must have hated him.
That's your motive.
As a nurse, you have easy access
to the drugs.
You can get drugs elsewhere.
A lot of drug stores out there
will sell you this sort of drugs.
You said it yourself, I'm a nurse,
I'm unlikely to mix up the drugs.
That's why we suspect someone else.
Who else is there?
Who else has a motive,
knows Tai Yat-kin well
and has the chance to do it?
You suspect Suet?
She's the prime suspect.
But we have no proof.
That's why we came to ask you
if you noticed anything odd about her.
Did she ask you about glucose
inhibitors beforehand?
No.
I didn't notice anything odd about her.
She also didn't ask me anything about drugs.
She was browsing online that morning.
Was she checking on glucose inhibitors?
When she bought the recording pen,
she said she needed to get something else.
She bought oolong tea.
Tai Yat-kin was drinking oolong tea.
She spiked the oolong tea?
I need to get money from the mini storage.
I won't go with you.
I still have errands to run.
OK. I'll go this way.
I go that way.
See you at home.
Did Suet pick up the glucose inhibitor
from the drug store after that?
I shouldn't say that.
What if I was overthinking?
(Pharmacist's Tip...Avoid drinking alcohol)
(Alcohol can increase the
drug's side effects...)
(and may cause low blood sugar)
Did she kill him?
Luckily, you had two recording pens
and managed to record
Tai Yat-kin's confession.
It was Suet's idea.
She bought an extra recording pen
because she had another plan?
She wanted Tai Yat-kin dead from the start?
Why did she do it?
Since we already have the evidence,
why must Tai Yat-kin die?
I need to call the Police.
No, you can't.
I perjured myself,
the cops would arrest me too.
Was she worried if Tai Yat-kin went to jail,
she'll be exposed of perjury?
Was she scared?
But she really could have died.
Was it worth it?
What's her reason?
Have another one.
You made a recording?
You think you'll get me talking?
Stop hitting me. Check the recording pen.
There are no batteries.
The broad wanted me to get evidence.
I bought the recording pen to humor her.
What now?
You were thinking of a way
to make the broad cough up the money.
Call her now.
Tell her you saw through our plan.
Pretend you kidnapped me
and tell her to pay a ransom.
If she refused, tell her you'll kill me.
She trusts me, she'll pay the ransom.
Let's try that.
It's a kidnapping. I need to tie you up.
The whole nine yards.
These are the messages between Ben and me.
When did she get ahold of my phone?
Wait...these messages are transposed.
These are messages from Ben's phone.
Did Suet have Ben's phone?
Cathy, what are you doing?
The bag was dirty,
I was going to empty it out and wash it.
No, I can manage.
It's OK...don't let Cathy spot anything.
Cathy...you have the afternoon off tomorrow?
Yes!
Let's go to the beach.
We didn't get to go last time.
Great! Which one?
I'll let you decide.
I'm almost there. Are you off yet?
(Ko Sir calling)
You didn't text me back.
I was afraid you had to work OT
and blow me off again.
I will work very hard to make a lot of money
and buy the prettiest and biggest castle
so you and I can move in together.
I had fun building a castle today.
Today is the happiest day of my life.
You're too old for a fantasy, silly.
This is fun, but this is made of sand.
It'll be washed away
and you'll have nothing left.
If I can't have it,
it's nice to just look at it.
When the next wave moves in,
there's nothing to look at.
Haven't you heard? You won't leave
a trace in the water,
But life is different.
If you did something,
you'll leave traces, however small they are,
people will always find out.
Did you find out something?
Though I don't entirely know why you did it.
It broke my heart just the same.
But one must bear the consequence
of one's mistakes.
Miss Ho Pui-suet,
you're suspected of murdering Tai Yat-kin.
Please come with us.
You called them?
I did not.
You're someone dearest to me.
But you betrayed me!
You said you have forgiven me
and treated me as your best friend.
It was a lie, wasn't it?
Why did you do it? Why? Why?
I did not.
I never intended to hurt you.
Save it.
I don't want to listen to you.
Miss Ho, please calm down.
Miss Tse didn't call us.
We were unable to contact her
and we suspect she was covering up for you.
We looked for her in the hospital
and found out you might be here.
I'm sorry...
I intended to persuade you
to turn yourself in.
Sorry, I should have told you.
Thanks for coming with me today.
I'll always remember today.
Baby, can you have breakfast
with me tomorrow?
Why can't we have dinner together?
Why are you fixated on breakfast?
Because breakfast is the
happiest time of the day.
Having someone to eat breakfast with
is happier than happy.
I didn't know you're a breakfast person.
I don't usually get up this early.
But I want to be with you.
I think eating breakfast with someone
is a very happy thing.
Pictures from an instant camera
have a different feeling.
I like the surprise.
You'll never know what you captured.
Why would someone young like you
like something so old fashioned?
Age has nothing to do with it.
You never know what you captured.
I like the surprise.
The adult world is so exhausting.
Let's do something stupid
and play with the sand on the beach.
Looks like you want to go to the beach.
Yes, I know it's childish, but fun.
I will work very hard to make a lot of money
and buy the prettiest and biggest castle
so you and I can move in together.
If I can't have it,
it's nice to just look at it.
Cathy is honest and kind.
She can't bear to have a friend
who was a murderer.
Ho Pui-suet, you are charged with
the murder of Tai Yat-kin.
How do you plead?
Guilty.
Why did you kill the victim?
Listen, whoever stands between
me and my money,
I don't care if it's the chick inside,
or the nurse out there.
I'll kill them both.
I was afraid if Tai Yat-kin was arrested,
the whole thing will come to light.
He'd say I committed perjury
to protect him.
I didn't want to go to jail.
Tai Yat-kin was a lunatic.
He told me if I didn't do as he said,
he'd get someone to rape me and kill me.
I had to protect myself.
Compared to yourself,
you're even more afraid of him hurting me.
It wasn't self-protection.
You were protecting me.
I was scared. I feared him.
He went too far and made me do it.
If you want to nail him,
let's nail this creep. I'll help you.
Just tell me what to do.
You didn't do it for yourself.
Everything you did, you did it for me.
For me, no matter how scared you were,
you went ahead and did it
with no second thoughts.
To be able to do one thing
for someone I love,
I have no regrets.
Next time, let's target for
the outlying islands.
OK! You're recovering so well.
I think it'll happen soon.
What about you?
I saw on the news,
Suet pleaded guilty in court.
I don't quite understand why she did it.
She did it for someone
she really cared about
and wanted to help someone fulfill a wish.
That's why she sacrificed herself.
Just like you did it for Ben,
and took such good care of me.
you're determined to get well.
I'm determined, but I'm doing it for you.
I don't want to become such a burden.
Besides, I promised you I will try hard.
Your seasonal drink, hot pumpkin latte.
Thanks.
Thank you.
It tastes better with cardamom powder.
Try it.
See?
You're right.
Try it.
Thank you.
We should come here often for coffee.
And try all their seasonal drinks.